export default data = [
  {
      question: "The ballet dancers’ ______ movements delighted all the audience",
      options: ["truthful","doubtful","graceful","helpful"],
      correct_option: "graceful"
  },
  {
      question: "At the closing ceremony of the Olympic Games, all the athletes ______ good-bye to the audience",
      options: ["charmed","waved","dared","gazed"],
      correct_option: "waved"
  },
  {
      question: "The drug problem is universal.  It is not ______ to one country",
      options: ["protected","detected","admitted","restricted"],
      correct_option: "restricted"
  },
  {
      question: "I think that this new program will be ______ of your effort",
      options: ["cautious","fruitful","worthy","patient"],
      correct_option: "worthy"
  },
  {
      question: "This textbook is ______ more difficult to read than the other one",
      options: ["considerably","favorably","desirably","respectably"],
      correct_option: "considerably"
  },
  {
      question: "The ______ of Linda’s love for music made her fly to Vienna to enter a music school",
      options: ["quantity","intensity","creativity","formality"],
      correct_option: "intensity"
  },
  {
      question: "E-mail plays a ______ role in modern communication",
      options: ["vital","violent","vivid","various"],
      correct_option: "vital"
  },
  {
      question: "I ______ accept your plan, but I think it should be somewhat reworded",
      options: ["basically","leisurely","modestly","properly"],
      correct_option: "basically"
  },
  {
      question: "This poem may be ______ in several different ways and each of them makes sense",
      options: ["negotiated","designated","interpreted","substituted"],
      correct_option: "interpreted"
  },
  {
      question: "The ______ of this piece of cloth is too coarse.  Do you have a finer one?",
      options: ["content","display","extent","texture"],
      correct_option: "texture"
  },
  {
      question: "His plan ______ in failure though it had been supported by many people",
      options: ["held on","ended up","put away","brought about"],
      correct_option: "ended up"
  },
  {
      question: "Sara enjoys amusing her friends by ______ stories",
      options: ["speaking out","setting off","making up","giving away"],
      correct_option: "making up"
  },
  {
      question: "As the applause ______ , the curtain on the stage dropped slowly",
      options: ["took off","died down","passed out","stayed up"],
      correct_option: "died down"
  },
  {
      question: "No one can possibly know ______ when an earthquake will strike",
      options: ["in advance","in particular","in vain","in case"],
      correct_option: "in advance"
  },
  {
      question: "The scientist’s project to build a modern laboratory was ______  on account of its huge budget",
      options: ["taken for granted","started out","got into difficulty","called into question"],
      correct_option: "called into question"
  },
]
